

Adeitan Doluwamu

Fullstack Developer/ Product designer

With over three years of experience in Fullstack development and Product designing, I am confident I will be an excellent fit for Frontend Developer, Backend Developer and even Product Designer roles. My experience has provided me with the innovative and technical skills necessary to successfully provide any company with multifaceted technical solutions across a wide range of software platforms.

Contact

Phone

+234-901-9307-489

Email

adoluwamu@gmail.com

LinkedIn

linkedin.com/in/doluwamu-adeitan-41bab5201/

Github

github.com/doluwamu

Dribbble

https://dribbble.com/doluwamu

Education/Training

2019 - Present

Economics

University Of Lagos

2019 - 2020

Intro to web development(Computer)
Aptech

Technologies

- JavaScript
- Nestis
- TypeScript
- Nextis
- UI/UX
- Figma
- Reactis
- CSS
- Nodejs
- HTML
- MySQL/PostgreSQL
- SCSS
- MongoDB
- Python

Languages

English

Yoruba

Experience

June 2021 - Aug 2021 Christ Image Assembly

Product Designer

Worked with a team as the only product designer for a church's application. I was responsible for revamping the design for the existing pages as well as designing new screens for the app. The major technology used was Figma.

July 2022 - Sept 2022 Rock Tennis Foundation

FullStack Developer

Worked as a fullstack developer on a website for a tennis foundation in Ogun state. The technologies used were React and NodeJs. I was responsible for the building of both the frontend and backend. I built and admin page where admins could Create, Edit, Delete and also view details that will be displayed on the main website and also built the main website for the foundation.

📍 Jan 2021 - Jan 2023

OrderEat

Backend Developer

Worked with a robust team of software engineers on for a food logistics company. Working on the backend, I was responsible for updating existing endpoint and making sure code written were clean, maintainable and scalable. I also created new endpoints where necessary. The technologies used were JavaScript and Python.I also joined the team in maintaining the codebase to ensure the app is up to date with current technologies and best practices to ensure the code base is easily understood by developers who may work on it later in the future.

June 2023 - PresentFoode

Lead Product Designer

Working as the product designer for a startup app called Foode. As the lead designer, I am responsible for designing and wireframing the UI and interactions for the flow of the app. The technology I utilized for this is Figma. I also interviewed incoming designer and frontend developers for the startup. I have shared a portion of the design on my dribbble page with the permission of the company: https://dribbble.com/shots/22127723-Foode-E-commerce-app.

Volunteering

Sept 2022 - June 2023 GDSC Unilag

Tutor